CONFIDENCE EFEM

WEB DEVELOPER



- **1** 09122641558
- ✓ confidenceefem1@gmail.com
- 2 11 Oduduwa Street, Apapa, Lagos
- https://github.com/ConfidenceEfem

PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional web developer with a years plus of experience in backend as a service and frontend development. I have strong creative and analytical skills with an eye for detail. I am also the team lead for the second runner up of **Genz hackathon**. I have worked with 2 startup and currently open to work with more

SKILLS

- ReactJS
- Material UI
- NodeJS
- UI/UX
- Firebase
- Problem-Solving
- Antd
- Strong Communication

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Codelab

2022-Present

• Web Development

FRONTEND INSTRUCTOR

Mandavo Computer learning Center

2022 - Present

· Train and equip undergraduate with tech skill

BACKEND DEVELOPER

Frixx Limited

2022 - Present

- Create a waitlist API
- Build strong and secured authentication, authorization and validation for users using REST API

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Happy World College

2015 - 2021

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

Nnamdi Azikwe University 2022 - presently

PROJECTS

- https://earli.finance
- https://smart-dev.netlify.app
- https://artik-app.netlify.app
- https://teenhoodinandout.netlify.app
- https://smartcoin.netlify.app